http://www.bible-reading.com/privacy.html

Bible-Reading.com Privacy Statement
Bible-Reading.com >
Web Site Tools > Privacy StatementWhat's New? (Aug 8, 2000)[ ... |Search|Stats|Chat|Site Map|What's New?|Changed Pages|Top Pages|Privacy Statement|Awards]
Have you used the Bible Reading Calendar?
Bible-Reading.com Privacy Statement
All users of Bible-Reading.com retain complete anonymity where Bible-Reading.com is concerned. Bible-Reading.com does not acquire or collect any personal information about you, except when you choose to sign our public guestbook. Your name, location, and email address all remain your private properties. Bible-Reading.com does, however, collect information which is specific to how you entered and use our site. Our server notes details such as the server you are logged onto, the geographic location of the ISP you use, the type of browser you use, your IP address, and what site "referred" you to bible-Reading.com. This information is obtained for a variety of purposes, including customization of your visit here and optimization of search engine rankings.
Cookies are not currently used by Bible-reading.com, although they are used by our ad broker, Burst Media.
Cookies may be added in the future to allow users to personalize features on the web site.
Any information gathered on Bible-Reading.com will be kept strictly confidential.
If you have questions about this privacy statement, please contact me.
DISCLOSURE: We may earn a commission when you use one of our coupons/links to make a purchase.
Privacy Statement - Broken Links / Suggestions / CommentsCopyright © 1995-2020 Bible-Reading.com - Page last modified E-mail toMichael
